<resources>
    <string name="app_name">30 CyberSecurity Tips</string>
    <string name="cybertip1">01. Use Strong, Unique Passwords</string>
    <string name="cybertip2">02. Enable Two-Factor Authentication (2FA)</string>
    <string name="cybertip3">03. Regularly Update Software</string>
    <string name="cybertip4">04. Beware of Phishing Scams</string>
    <string name="cybertip5">05. Secure Your Wi-Fi Network</string>
    <string name="cybertip6">06. Use a VPN on Public Networks</string>
    <string name="cybertip7">07. Back Up Your Data Regularly</string>
    <string name="cybertip8">08. Install Antivirus Software</string>
    <string name="cybertip9">09. Be Cautious with Downloads</string>
    <string name="cybertip10">10. Secure Your Smartphone</string>
    <string name="cybertip11">11. Check App Permissions</string>
    <string name="cybertip12">12. Use Secure Connections for Payments</string>
    <string name="cybertip13">13. Educate Yourself About Cyber Threats</string>
    <string name="cybertip14">14. Limit Personal Information on Social Media</string>
    <string name="cybertip15">15. Encrypt Sensitive Data</string>
    <string name="cybertip16">16. Secure Physical Devices</string>
    <string name="cybertip17">17. Beware of Shoulder Surfing</string>
    <string name="cybertip18">18. Avoid Using Public Charging Stations</string>
    <string name="cybertip19">19. Manage Social Engineering Risks</string>
    <string name="cybertip20">20. Monitor Your Accounts for Suspicious Activity</string>
    <string name="cybertip21">21. Implement Network Security Measures</string>
    <string name="cybertip22">22. Practice Safe Browsing</string>
    <string name="cybertip23">23. Dispose of Digital Media Securely</string>
    <string name="cybertip24">24. Secure Your Home Network</string>
    <string name="cybertip25">25. Beware of Wi-Fi Sniffing</string>
    <string name="cybertip26">26. Use Secure Email Practices</string>
    <string name="cybertip27">27. Secure Cloud Storage</string>
    <string name="cybertip28">28. Understand and Manage Cookies</string>
    <string name="cybertip29">29. Be Cautious with Internet of Things (IoT) Devices</string>
    <string name="cybertip30">30. Learn to Recognize Secure Sites</string>
    <string name="description1">Craft passwords that are complex, incorporating a mix of uppercase and lowercase letters, numbers, and symbols. Avoid using easily guessable information like birthdays or names. Each of your online accounts should have a unique password to prevent a single breach from compromising all your accounts.</string>
    <string name="description2">Enhance security by adding a second verification step after entering your password. This can be a code sent to your phone or generated by an app. It ensures that even if someone obtains your password, they would still need the second factor to access your account.</string>
    <string name="description3">Keep all software, including operating systems and applications, up to date. Developers regularly release updates to patch security vulnerabilities. Delaying updates leaves you open to attacks exploiting known weaknesses.</string>
    <string name="description4">Phishing scams trick you into divulging personal information, such as passwords and credit card numbers, by mimicking legitimate communications from trusted entities. Always verify the authenticity of requests for information and never click on suspicious links.</string>
    <string name="description5">Protect your Wi-Fi with a robust password and the latest encryption standard (like WPA3). Conceal your network from public view by disabling the broadcast of your network name (SSID). This prevents unauthorized users from attempting to join your network.</string>
    <string name="description6">Public Wi-Fi networks are not secure, making your data vulnerable to interception. A Virtual Private Network (VPN) encrypts your internet connection, safeguarding your privacy and security when using public Wi-Fi.</string>
    <string name="description7">Protect yourself against data loss from ransomware attacks, theft, or hardware failure by regularly backing up important data. Use diverse methods like cloud storage and external drives for redundancy.</string>
    <string name="description8">Use reputable antivirus software to provide real-time protection against malware, including viruses, spyware, and ransomware. Regularly update your antivirus software to detect and prevent the latest threats.</string>
    <string name="description9">Download files and applications only from reputable sources. Malicious software can be disguised as legitimate apps, compromising your devices security upon installation.</string>
    <string name="description10">Apply security measures such as screen locks, biometric authentication, and remote wipe capabilities. Regularly update your devices operating system and apps to protect against vulnerabilities.</string>
    <string name="description11">Review the permissions requested by apps to ensure they only have access to necessary information. Unnecessary permissions can expose sensitive data or control over your device to malicious actors.</string>
    <string name="description12">When making online payments, verify that the website uses HTTPS, ensuring an encrypted connection. Stick to well-known and reputable payment platforms and services.</string>
    <string name="description13">Stay informed about the latest cyber threats and how to defend against them. Awareness is your first line of defense in the constantly evolving landscape of cybersecurity threats.</string>
    <string name="description14">Be mindful of the information you share on social media. Oversharing can make you a target for identity theft and other cybercrimes. Adjust your privacy settings to control who can see your posts.</string>
    <string name="description15">Use encryption tools to protect sensitive information on your devices and in emails. Encryption scrambles your data, making it unreadable to anyone without the decryption key.</string>
    <string name="description16">Use physical locks for laptops and encrypt hard drives to protect against theft. Enable tracking services to locate or remotely wipe devices that are lost or stolen.</string>
    <string name="description17">Be aware of your surroundings, especially when entering sensitive information on your device in public places. Shoulder surfers can steal information by directly observing your screen or keypad.</string>
    <string name="description18">Public charging stations can be compromised to deliver malware to your device. Use your charger or a portable battery pack to avoid this risk.</string>
    <string name="description19">Social engineering attacks manipulate individuals into divulging confidential information. Be skeptical of unsolicited communications asking for sensitive information, and verify their authenticity.</string>
    <string name="description20">Regularly review your financial and online accounts for unauthorized transactions or accesses. Early detection of suspicious activity can prevent further damage.</string>
    <string name="description21">Enhance your networks security with firewalls, encryption, and secure Wi-Fi settings. Regularly update your routers firmware and change default passwords to protect against unauthorized access.</string>
    <string name="description22">Navigate the internet cautiously, avoiding suspicious websites and pop-ups. Use web browser security settings and extensions that block malicious sites and ads.</string>
    <string name="description23">Before disposing of or selling electronic devices, ensure all personal data is completely erased. Use data destruction software to overwrite the data, making it unrecoverable.</string>
    <string name="description24">Change default router passwords, regularly update the routers firmware, and disable features not in use, such as WPS or remote management, to secure your home network against external threats.</string>
    <string name="description25">Wi-Fi sniffing can intercept the data transmitted over unsecured wireless networks. Always use encrypted connections and avoid transmitting sensitive information over public Wi-Fi.</string>
    <string name="description26">Secure your email communications by using strong passwords, enabling two-factor authentication, and encrypting sensitive emails. Be cautious of phishing attempts and unsolicited attachments.</string>
    <string name="description27">Use strong passwords and enable two-factor authentication for cloud storage accounts. Consider encrypting files locally before uploading them to the cloud for an additional layer of security.</string>
    <string name="description28">Cookies track your online activity and can compromise your privacy. Regularly clear your cookies and manage your browsers cookie settings to limit tracking.</string>
    <string name="description29">IoT devices can be vulnerable to attacks. Change default passwords, regularly update the devices firmware, and ensure they are connected to a secure network to protect against unauthorized access.</string>
    <string name="description30">Look for HTTPS in the websites URL and a padlock icon in the browsers address bar to verify a sites security. Secure sites encrypt the data transmitted, protecting your information from interception.</string>


</resources>